<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MediKeen</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">HomePage</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="doctorinfo">Which doctor you are finding?</string>
    <string name="doctorinfo1">We\'ll help you to find doctor</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="create">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search">Doctor List</string>
    <string name="title_activity_prescription">Prescription</string>
    <string name="title_activity_doctorprofile">Doctor Profile</string>
    <string name="title_pharmakit_menu">PharmaKit Menu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_map">Map</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close drawer</string>
    <string name="threehr">3hr delivery 15% off</string>
    <string name="eighthr">8hr delivery 20% off</string>
    <string name="title">Welcome to MediKeen!</string>
    <string name="titleDesc">Thank you for using our products and Services (as defined below)\n\nThis terms of use agreement ("Agreement") governs users ("You", the "User(s)") using Services provided by us ("Pharmakit") as a platform for quality health services including but not limited to place and purchase healthcare and medicinal products of various manufacturing brands (collectively, "Products") online. Please read them carefully.\n\nThis Agreement should be read along with our Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="desc">BY USING THE WEBSITES OR BY CLICKING "I ACCEPT" BELOW, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.</string>
    <string name="elDesc">We require and assume that you have legal capacity to enter into this Agreement, as laid down by applicable laws of India.</string>
    <string name="srDesc"><b>Services</b> Acting as a platform between You and the for healthcare service providers (Participating Medical Professionals/Organization) we provide users of Pharmakit, an access to a wide array of resources through our network of properties which may be provided to you in a variety of mediums and devices now known or hereinafter developed including but not limited to mobile applications and online portals for placing and purchasing healthcare and medicinal products; patient management features, reference tools and applications, personalized content, continuing medical education, communication tools, medical records, medical history and discussion boards (collectively, the "Services"). 
         \n\n<b>Placing and Purchasing Products :</b>Once you upload your prescription, you will be deemed to have placed an order for the products mentioned in the prescription. Pharmakit shall not be liable to examine the authenticity of the order in terms of products ordered and the Users shall at all times ensure full compliance with the applicable provisions of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1940, the Drugs and Magic Remedies (Objectionable Advertisements) Act, 1954 and rules thereunder as applicable and as amended from time to time and also all applicable laws, rules and regulations (including, but not limited to sales tax/ VAT, income tax, octroi, service tax, central excise, custom duty, local levies etc.) regarding your use of Service and purchase, solicitation of offers to purchase, and sale of products or services through Pharamakit. You shall not engage in any transaction in an item or service, which is prohibited by the provisions of any applicable law including Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1940, the Drugs and Magic Remedies (Objectionable Advertisements) Act, 1954 or regulations for the time being in force. Please note that for some medicines which are sensitive to pharmacy rules, we will ask a genuine prescription to be verified before sale. 
         \n\n<b>Delivery of Products :</b>All products/services and information displayed on the Pharmakit’s website/ mobile app constitute an invitation to offer. Your order/ uploading your prescription for purchase of healthcare products; constitutes your offer which shall be subject to the terms and conditions of this mentioned herein. We reserve the right to accept or reject your offer in part or in full. Our acceptance of your order will take place upon dispatch of the product(s) ordered. Dispatch of all the product(s) ordered, may or may not happen at the same time, in such a scenario that portion of the order which has been dispatched will be deemed to have been accepted by us and the balance would continue to be on offer to us and we reserve the right to accept or reject such balance order. No act or omission of Pharmakit prior to the actual dispatch of the product (s) ordered will constitute acceptance of your offer. If you have supplied us with your email address or phone number, we will notify you by email and/or phone number, as the case may be, as soon as possible to confirm receipt of your order and email/contact you again to confirm dispatch and therefore acceptance of the order.
         \n\n <b>Upon Delivery :</b>Upon placing an order/ uploading the prescription, Pharmakit shall examine and if all the required conditions as per the applicable regulations are fulfilled, Pharmakit will deliver the products to you or to the person you have authorized for collection on your behalf, and be entitled to its payment for the same. Furthermore, incase of any delay in delivery, it is the responsibility of the User to inform Pharmakit if an order does not arrive within time.</string>
    <string name="phDesc"><b>Pharmakit Account:</b>You will need to register and create a Pharmakit Account in order to use our Services.
          \n\n<b>Protection of Account:</b>To protect your Pharmakit Account, keep your password confidential. You are responsible for the activity that happens on or through your Pharmakit Account. </string>
    <string name="scDesc"><b>Rights:</b>Pharmakit gives you a personal, worldwide, royalty-free, non-assignable and non-exclusive license for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the Services as provided by Pharmakit, in the manner permitted by these terms.
           \n\n<b>Own Judgment:</b>Our Services do not give professional advice or recommend particular products and should as a result, exercise their own clinical judgment as to the information they provide.
           \n\n<b>Third Party Content:</b>Our Services will display some content that is not Pharmakit’s. This content is the sole responsibility of the entity that makes it available. We may review content to determine whether it is illegal or violates our policies, and we may remove or refuse to display content that we reasonably believe violates our policies or the law.
           \n\n<b>Notifications:</b>In connection with your use of the Services, we may send you service announcements, administrative messages, and other information. You may opt out of some of those communications.
           \n\nOur Services are available on mobile devices. Do not use such Services in a way that distracts you and prevents you from obeying traffic or safety laws.</string>
    <string name="uDesc"><b>Content:</b>Some of our Services contain different interactive features where you are allowed to maintain electronic medical records (EMR), upload, submit, store, send or receive content ("Content"). You retain ownership of any intellectual property rights that you hold in that Content. In short, what belongs to you stays yours.
    \n\n<b>IPR of Your Content:</b>You certify that you own all intellectual and industrial property rights in Your Content. You hereby grant us, our affiliates, and our partners a worldwide, irrevocable, royalty-free, nonexclusive, sub licensable license to use, reproduce, create derivative works of, publicly communicate and distribute Your Content and subsequent versions of Your Content for the purposes of (i) displaying Your Content on our Sites, (ii) distributing Your Content, either electronically or via other media; and (iii) meaningful use. The rights you grant in this license are for the limited purpose of providing quality Services, operating, promoting, research purposes and improving our Services, and to develop new ones. This aforesaid license continues even if you stop using our Services. </string>
    <string name="pcDesc"><b>IPR:</b>Pharmakit’s Services include a combination of content that we create, that our partners create, and that our users create. Some materials published on our websites, apps, including, but not limited to, written content, photographs, graphics, images, illustrations, marks, logos are protected by our intellectual property (copyright) or industrial property rights (such as trademarks) or those of our partners or users.
           \n\n<b>No license:</b>Neither Pharmakit nor any of its partners or users grants You a license nor use authorisation over its intellectual or industrial property rights or over any other right or property concerning the website, app, its Services or its contents. Thus You may not copy, modify, publish, transmit, participate in the transfer or sale of, reproduce, create derivative works of, distribute, publicly communicate, or in any way exploit any of the materials or content on our website/ app/ content, in whole or in part.
           \n\n<b>Product Prices:</b>Reasonable due care has been taken to try and provide accurate data and information. MRP of products available through our Services will at all times be as accurate as possible however it could be possible that there is a difference in the MRP shown on by Pharmakit versus the actual MRP on our bill. Customer will be informed about any differences in MRP at the time of processing the order.</string>
    <string name="tDesc">We are constantly changing and improving our Services. We may add or remove f1unctionalities or features, and we may suspend or stop a Service altogether without any prior information and without assigning any reason.
         \n\nPharmakit may also stop providing Services to you, or add or create new limits to our Services at any time. The situations that may result in cancellation of any Services, without limitation, for instance, nonavailability of the product or quantities ordered by User, non- availability of the Service, inaccuracies or errors in pricing information, or problems identified by Pharmakits credit and fraud avoidance department.
         \n\nYou may also stop using our Services at any time, however, Pharmakit will not be able to cancel orders that have already been processed, it is pertinent to note that Pharmakit has the full right to decide whether an order has been processed or not. User hereby agrees and undertakes that the decision taken by Pharmakit is acceptable to User and User shall not create any dispute on the decision taken by Pharmakit on cancellation.</string>
    <string name="wDesc">Other than as expressly set out in this agreement, Pharmakit ((including but not limited to its, agent, employees, assignees, suppliers, partners) does not make any specific promises about the services. For example, we don’t make any commitments about the content within the services, the specific functions of the services, or their reliability, availability, or ability to meet your needs. We provide the services “as is”.
         \n\nSome jurisdictions provide for certain warranties, like the implied warranty of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. To the extent permitted by law, we exclude all warranties, express or implied, of any kind.</string>
    <string name="lDesc">When permitted by law, Pharmakit (including but not limited to its, agent, employees, assignees, suppliers, partners) will not be responsible for any transaction relating to availing of the services, lost profits, revenues, or data, financial losses or indirect, special, consequential, exemplary, or punitive damages.
          \n\nIn all cases, Pharmakit, and its suppliers and distributors, will not be liable for any loss or damage that is not reasonably foreseeable.</string>
    <string name="iDesc">You hereby agree to indemnify, defend and hold Pharmakit and all of Pharmakit’s directors, owners, employees, agents, information providers, affiliates, partners, advertisers and providers harmless from and against any and all liability, losses, costs, and expenses (including attorneys’ fees) incurred by any Pharmakit’s Party in connection with any claim, including, but not limited to, a breach of this Agreement, a breach of the applicable regulations and/or the infringement of rights owned by Pharmakit, its partners, other uses or any third party; claims for defamation, violation of rights of publicity and/or privacy, intellectual or industrial property rights infringement, arising out of :Your use of and/or connection to our Services; any use or alleged use of your accounts or your passwords by any person, whether or not authorized by you; the Content, the quality, or the performance of content that You submit to Pharmakit; your violation of the terms hereunder or applicable Regulations; your violation of the rights of any other person or entity; any submission of false, inaccurate or misleading information, acts that may cause direct or indirect damages to Pharmakit, other users or third parties.
         \n\nWe reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter for which you are required to indemnify us, and you agree to cooperate with our defense of these claims. </string>
    <string name="gDesc"><b>Acceptance:</b>Your use of these applications provided through our Services, constitutes your binding acceptance of the terms mentioned in the Agreement and our Privacy Policy, including any modifications that we make from time to time.
        \n\n<b>Modification:</b>We may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a Service to, for example, reflect changes to the law or changes to our Services. You should look at the terms regularly. We’ll post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. We’ll post notice of modified additional terms in the applicable Service. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen days after they are posted. However, changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for a Service, you should discontinue your use of that Service.
        \n\n<b>Content Syndication:</b>Listing and editorial content published on the Pharmakit site may be syndicated to carefully chosen partner sites that have a relevant audience without notification to the business app publishers. Should You prefer not to syndicate their content on third-party sites a written request should be sent to Pharmakit.
        \n\n<b>Jurisdiction:</b>Without prejudice to anything contained here in above, all differences, disputes etc., pertaining to the use of Services or any terms and conditions relating to this Agreement shall be subject to the sole and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts at Mumbai.
        \n\n<b>Dispute Resolution:</b>All differences, disputes etc., pertaining to the use of Services or any terms and conditions relating to this Agreement shall be resolved by arbitration in terms of the Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996 (Act). The arbitration shall be conducted by a sole arbitrator appointed by Pharmakit and in terms of the Act and the venue of arbitration shall be Mumbai. Either You or we may seek any interim or preliminary relief from a court of competent jurisdiction, in India, necessary to protect the rights or the property of You or Pharmakit (or its agents, suppliers, and subcontractors), pending the completion of arbitration.
        \n\nIf any part of these terms is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision, and the remainder of the terms shall continue in effect.</string>
    <string name="questions">For questions or concerns about these terms of use, please send an email to legal@pharmakit.co</string>
    <string name="crash_toast_text">Application crashed. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="take_picture">Take!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_frogot_password">Frogot Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_attach_prescription">Attach Prescription</string>
    <string name="title_activity_address_prescription">Address Prescription</string>
    <string name="title_activity_password_reset_code_verification">PasswordResetCodeVerificationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_password">NewPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">UserProfileActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_history_detail">HistoryDetailActivity</string>

</resources>